<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Computing on Not A Shopping Note</title>
    <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/tags/cloud-computing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Computing on Not A Shopping Note</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/tags/cloud-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 4 - Compute Layer</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-4/</guid>
      <description>Compute Layer www.awsacademy.com
Four compute model categories:
Virtual Machines (VMs):
EC2: elastic and sizeable virtual servers in cloud Lightsail: Virtual Private Server to run simple workloads Containers
Elastic Container Service (ECS): runs Docker container applications on AWS PaaS
Elastic Beanstalk: Runs web applications and services that are developed in Java, .NET, PHP, Node.js, Python, Ruby, Go, and Docker. Serverless
AWS Lambda: Serverless compute solution that runs Java, Go, PowerShell, Node.js, C#, Python, or Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 1 - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Course www.awsacademy.com
Definisi Layanan komputasi yang diletakkan di internet.
SAAS = Software as a Services, Software yang diletakkan diinternet. DIbayarkan per-orang atau per-kapasitas : (sperti sewa hotel)
Office 365 Instagram Meta Email PAAS = Platform as A Services (seperti sewa rumah). Di tagih berdasarkan konsumsi: berapa banyak dipakai.
Cloud Storage Elastic Benastalk IAAS = Infrastructure as A Services (seperti sewa tanah), jargon Lift and Save
VM (Virtual Machine) On-premise (SHM) adalah punya server sendiri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 2 - Introducing Cloud Architecture</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-2/</guid>
      <description>Well-Architected Framework .
A guide that is designed to help you build the most secure, high-performing, resilient, and efficient infrastructure possible for your cloud applications and workloads.
Security: the ability to protect information, systems, and assets while delivering business value through risk assessments and mitigation strategies. The implementation: strong identity foundation, enable traceability, security at all layers, automate security best practices,and protect data in transit and at rest.
Operational Excellence: the ability to run systems and gain insight into their operations to deliver business value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
