<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New-notashoppingnotes on Not A Shopping Note</title>
    <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New-notashoppingnotes on Not A Shopping Note</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 4 - Compute Layer</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-4/</guid>
      <description>Compute Layer www.awsacademy.com
Four compute model categories:
Virtual Machines (VMs):
EC2: elastic and sizeable virtual servers in cloud Lightsail: Virtual Private Server to run simple workloads Containers
Elastic Container Service (ECS): runs Docker container applications on AWS PaaS
Elastic Beanstalk: Runs web applications and services that are developed in Java, .NET, PHP, Node.js, Python, Ruby, Go, and Docker. Serverless
AWS Lambda: Serverless compute solution that runs Java, Go, PowerShell, Node.js, C#, Python, or Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 4 - The IoT Security Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-4/</guid>
      <description>Penetration Testing Assessing the organization&amp;rsquo;s IoT requires testing hardware and software. Penetration testing should be done regularly throughout the lifecycle. Many regulations also require third-party penetration tests as it is a good security practice.
Furthermore, blue teams should ealuate the security posture while read teams are conducting their exercies.
Red and Blue Teams Penetration testing, with the goal of find and report vulnerabilities, should be limited to most important aspects of an implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 2 - Vulnerability Threat and Countermeasures</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-2/</guid>
      <description>Pillar of Information Security Five pillars of cybersecurtiy:
Confidentiality Integrity Availability Authentication Non-repudiation Plus two more in IoT
Resilience: maintain state of awareness and an accepted level of operational normalcy in response to disturbances including from the nature. Safety: safe from causing hurt, injury, or loss. TVR (Threat Vulnerability Risk) Threat: potential of attacks/exploit. Threat actor (source): who do the threat. Threat: hardware, software, environmental, supply chain, degradation, etc. Can target safety: transfer functions, state filters (kalman filters) and other inner control loop artifacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 1 - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Course www.awsacademy.com
Definisi Layanan komputasi yang diletakkan di internet.
SAAS = Software as a Services, Software yang diletakkan diinternet. DIbayarkan per-orang atau per-kapasitas : (sperti sewa hotel)
Office 365 Instagram Meta Email PAAS = Platform as A Services (seperti sewa rumah). Di tagih berdasarkan konsumsi: berapa banyak dipakai.
Cloud Storage Elastic Benastalk IAAS = Infrastructure as A Services (seperti sewa tanah), jargon Lift and Save
VM (Virtual Machine) On-premise (SHM) adalah punya server sendiri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 2 - Introducing Cloud Architecture</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/cloud-2/</guid>
      <description>Well-Architected Framework .
A guide that is designed to help you build the most secure, high-performing, resilient, and efficient infrastructure possible for your cloud applications and workloads.
Security: the ability to protect information, systems, and assets while delivering business value through risk assessments and mitigation strategies. The implementation: strong identity foundation, enable traceability, security at all layers, automate security best practices,and protect data in transit and at rest.
Operational Excellence: the ability to run systems and gain insight into their operations to deliver business value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 1 - A Brave New World</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-1/</guid>
      <description>Definition of IoT Based on IEEE, IoT is a network that connects uniquely identifiable “things” to the Internet. The “things” have sensing/actuation and potential programmability capabilities.
Based on ITU-T Y.2060 A device is a piece of equipment with the mandatory capabilities of communication and the optional capabilities of sensing, actuation, data capture, data storage, and data processing. Thing is an object of the physical world (physical things) or the information world (virtual things), which is capable of being identified and integrated into communication networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Template</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>Hello World Hi, im here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
