<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Network and Security on Not A Shopping Note</title>
    <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/categories/network-and-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Network and Security on Not A Shopping Note</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/categories/network-and-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 4 - The IoT Security Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-4/</guid>
      <description>Penetration Testing Assessing the organization&amp;rsquo;s IoT requires testing hardware and software. Penetration testing should be done regularly throughout the lifecycle. Many regulations also require third-party penetration tests as it is a good security practice.
Furthermore, blue teams should ealuate the security posture while read teams are conducting their exercies.
Red and Blue Teams Penetration testing, with the goal of find and report vulnerabilities, should be limited to most important aspects of an implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 2 - Vulnerability Threat and Countermeasures</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-2/</guid>
      <description>Pillar of Information Security Five pillars of cybersecurtiy:
Confidentiality Integrity Availability Authentication Non-repudiation Plus two more in IoT
Resilience: maintain state of awareness and an accepted level of operational normalcy in response to disturbances including from the nature. Safety: safe from causing hurt, injury, or loss. TVR (Threat Vulnerability Risk) Threat: potential of attacks/exploit. Threat actor (source): who do the threat. Threat: hardware, software, environmental, supply chain, degradation, etc. Can target safety: transfer functions, state filters (kalman filters) and other inner control loop artifacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security 1 - A Brave New World</title>
      <link>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devismail2y.github.io/notashoppingnote/new-notashoppingnote/iot-security-1/</guid>
      <description>Definition of IoT Based on IEEE, IoT is a network that connects uniquely identifiable “things” to the Internet. The “things” have sensing/actuation and potential programmability capabilities.
Based on ITU-T Y.2060 A device is a piece of equipment with the mandatory capabilities of communication and the optional capabilities of sensing, actuation, data capture, data storage, and data processing. Thing is an object of the physical world (physical things) or the information world (virtual things), which is capable of being identified and integrated into communication networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
